[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 56, "question": "Regardless of his capacity?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 57, "answer": "Regardless of whatever he's going to do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trayvon Martin"], "PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}, "docId": "120405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 63, "question": "What is your overview as we sit here tonight of this case?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "Well, I think it's very fair for the family of Trayvon Martin to be asking the question why George Zimmerman wasn't arrested.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "Tell me this, why is he seen in handcuffs if he hasn't been arrested?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "Well, we're not clear on whether he's been arrested or not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "How significant will that be to this debate, Charles, if that is true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "MD", "IN", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charles"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Shakespeare"]}, "docId": "120405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "IN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "IN", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "What do you think of the \"Stand Your Ground\" law in relation to this case?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "Well, there in lies the rub as Shakespeare might have said, because after all, we don't know what the exact facts are.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 158, "question": "Would you imagine, Gloria, very quickly, that there will be an arrest and indictment very soon in relation to George Zimmerman?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "EX", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "CC", "NN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 159, "answer": "There may very well be.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gloria", "George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "Mark Geragos, would you agree with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "Yes, I don't think it's going to be any sooner than five days or so.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mark Geragos"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Geragos", "Allred", "Zimmerman"]}, "docId": "120405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "VBG", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 177, "question": "What do you make of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 178, "answer": "My instinct as just a citizen, I'm not a professional like Geragos and Allred, I remember first hearing about it and hearing Zimmerman on the phone.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "What do you feel about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "In this situation, I don't think it's a case of working on either/or in our society.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 235, "question": "If I shot Justin Bieber, would I be out tonight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Justin Bieber"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 250, "question": "How old is your son?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 251, "answer": "He's 12.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 253, "question": "He's Arsenio Jr., right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 254, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Arsenio Jr."]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "What do you say to him post-Trayvon Martin about walking on his own now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "JJ", "NNP", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "I'm totally confused.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Martin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 274, "question": "How did you find it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 275, "answer": "Well, I think the scariest thing was when you get there and they take your phone and give you one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "Did you ever imagine the day would come where you'd have Magic Johnson owner of the Dodgers and Barack Obama president of the United States in your lifetime?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "Yes, it's amazing.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Magic Johnson", "Dodgers", "United States"], "PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Peter Max"]}, "docId": "120405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "Where is that jacket?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "At Peter Max's house.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJS", "NNS", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", ",", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 372, "question": "What was she really like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 373, "answer": "That was one of the reasons I really thought this book should be written, is that most people really didn't know her, including members of the press who actually covered her during that period of time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 383, "question": "How did they get on when the door was closed and they were left with just agents like you who saw everything?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 384, "answer": "ILL: They were very close, very much in love.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "And you're witnessing such private moments of great joy and great despair?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "Well, I had a great deal of concern about their welfare and well being.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 415, "question": "Clint, whenever you see those images, those images, what do you feel so long after that event?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 416, "answer": "Well, that never really leaves my consciousness.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "Is that's what's going through your mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "POS", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mrs. Kennedy"]}, "docId": "120405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 431, "question": "When did you realize that the president was probably dead?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "After I got up on the car and Mrs. Kennedy came up on the trunk to retrieve some material that had gone off to the right rear from the president's wound in his head, I put her back in the seat.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 440, "question": "How has that responsibility borne down on you over the years since then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 441, "answer": "Well, I've always felt a sense of guilt.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1990"], "LOCATION": ["Dallas"]}, "docId": "120405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "When you look back on that, is there anything you could have done?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "Well, I went back to Dallas in 1990.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBD", "CD", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 458, "question": "How many people were on the detail that day?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "At that time, there were 34 assigned to the president.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "Was she able to speak to you at all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "She was in shock.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "Do you believe Lee Harvey Oswald was just a man acting alone?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lee Harvey Oswald"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 493, "question": "What's your favorite of your time with her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "We had some wonderful times.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 519, "question": "Katherine, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 520, "answer": "I'm good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 521, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "I can't quite believe what's happening to you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 528, "question": "Can you believe what's going on here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 529, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 539, "question": "Is it weird to be over here now with this huge army of new fans who think that Katherine Jenkins, great dancer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 540, "answer": "ENKINS: It is funny because, you know, when I have been here before to make albums, it's been pretty much sort of under the radar.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Katherine Jenkins"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "Are you having fun or is it incredibly hard work?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "It's hard work, but it's fun.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 552, "question": "Is he single?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 553, "answer": "No, he's got a girlfriend.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 560, "question": "Yes, because it's been a bit of a tough time for you, hasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 561, "answer": "It has been.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 578, "question": "What do you want to say about it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 579, "answer": "Just, like you said, this is something to me that feels like really old news.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Afghanistan", "Iraq"]}, "docId": "120405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "RP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 591, "question": "What's been the big high for you professionally outside of what's going on now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "Honestly, it would be going out to entertain the troops in Afghanistan and Iraq.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "What's going on here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "I know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 611, "question": "Is that the ultimate Holy Grail for any big singer now, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 612, "answer": "ENKINS: Well, I think, you know, singing has always been my big passion in life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 621, "question": "What do you think he would make of his little girl now conquering America on the dance floor?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 622, "answer": "Oh, well, you know, I hope that he would be -- he would be happy and proud.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}]